girl I'm so excited for this Eric Brown
rally he's my hero really I couldn't
tell can you blame me this state is
about to have its first black Governor
aren't you
pumped forgive me for not being overly
enthusiastic about a former heavyweight
champion running our state um it's light
heavyweight besides girl won't it be
great to have someone in the governor's
mansion that actually cares about our
community obviously I just don't think
that's Eric Brown I've read his campaign
website a black Governor would be great
but aren't victories like that a little
Hollow when the candidate is more
focused on upholding the same racist
systems within our government as their
white predecessors God you were so
negative it's starting ladies and
gentlemen
introducing your main event weighing in
at already 170 lb and an undefeated
record of 47 wins no losses your
gubernatorial candidate and current
light heavyweight champion of the world
see what I mean man of the people all
right y settle down settle down be quiet
please now first item on my agenda if
I'm elected I'm locking all of you
up oh yeah
[Music]